NGUYỄN ANH VŨ

WEB DEVELOPER



- nguyenanhvu.work@gmail.com
- District 12, Ho Chi Minh City
- homiedev.com
- https://github.com/devnav2902

PROFILE

A web developer with 1 years of experience in the industry seeking a position front-end web developer. I believe that my technical skills and knowledge of HTML, CSS and JavaScript will render me a valuable addition to your web development team. I'm passionate about developing interactive websites and web features to drive up online traffic and sales.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- React.js (Redux, Ant Design, Gatsby.js, React Hook Form)
- TypeScript
- Laravel
- MySQL
- REST API
- Responsive Web Design

EXPERIENCE

TK SMART VISION (TITKUL COMPANY)

2021 - 2022

- Worked with back-end team to create web products
- Update UI
- Fix bugs

LITTLE PEOPLE (TITKUL COMPANY)

2021 - 2022

- · Worked with back-end team to create web products
- Create new feature

EDUCATION

HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF TRANSPORT

2018 - 2022

PERSONAL PROJECTS

HOMIEDEV (2020 - ONGOING)

• Creating a front-end blog with Gatsby.js

COURSEWE (2021 - 2022)

- https://github.com/devnav2902/coursewe-fe
- Creating an online learning and teaching marketplace
- Using React UI library Antd for Project
- Learn how to use Redux Toolkit with TypeScript
- Build a REST API With Laravel
- Validate forms with React Hook Form